{
    "id": "0e9b8b6a6b35461992a4c8786da4912e",
    "title": "Sentence Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The state of affairs .................................... sure to cause him anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The introduction of reforms ...................................... not liked by the aristocracy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Bread and butter ................................... wholesome.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Slow and steady ....................................... the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Silver as well as gold ..................................... a precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "James together with his friends ....................................... present at the venue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the old man nor his sons ......................................... able to give a satisfactory explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of the two plans ..................................... approved.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The jury ...................................... divided in their opinions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Thrice-told Tales ..................................... an interesting book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}